Thank you for watching
Blood Donation Appreciation Live
Okay...
The name of the live project that you will be performing in is...
It's the culmination of a project called the Voices for Life Blood Donation Promotion Project.
It's called the "Voices for Life Blood Donation Appreciation Live" today.
Today's live performance, as well as today's audience, is a culmination of the project.
There are many people who can't make it to the venue.
So we want to let everyone know about this project.
We will put this kind of post in the blood donation room.
We're going to put up these mailboxes in the blood donation rooms so that people who donate blood can write letters of encouragement to those who donate blood and wish them good luck.
They write letters of encouragement to those who donate blood.
They write to us with a lot of seriousness, don't they?
First of all, let me say hello to you.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Rack on to the hearts of our staff!
We are the super thrill center!
Pleased to meet you
Pleasure to meet you.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much for the rehearsal. Pleasure to meet you.
Definitely a rehearsal.
Better than earlier.
Seventy percent done.
Only 30% to go.
I just need to do my hair and bangs.
I hope that as many people as possible will understand and cooperate with our blood donation campaign.
I'd like to ask for your cooperation at today's show.
Thank you very much.
If only I had come a little earlier, I could have seen the eyelash making time.
We played a game like "Shotoku Taishi" (Prince Shotoku game).
Everyone had to pick a flavor they wanted to eat at the same time.
Was it hojicha pudding? That one.
There were many kinds of puddings, including hojicha pudding.
There were so many choices of hojicha pudding that we all had to choose the same one.
And everyone was so mature about it.
They were very mature and said, "I don't want this one.
That's all.
In the spring...
Because everyone gave it to me.
I'll have some hojicha.
You can have mascara.
I've been exposing my face to the waterfall belly so much I thought I'd read a little about it.
Everyone else is.
Me too.
Look at this half-face makeup!
When I put mascara on, I have so much more makeup on my face.
You see?
I put mascara on this one.
Mascara on this one, too.
I really love mascara.
I'm walking around with a hot nailer.
Oh, my God, my forehead.
I'm getting married.
Okay, that's it. Okay, what do I do?
I got it right here.
This lame is so cute. I'm using it here.
Is everything okay? I just remembered this club's content.
I remembered this morning.
I woke up this morning and I was like...
Oh, yeah, my stuff.
Today is Monday. We do this every Monday.
I thought it was my day.
I got on the train, and I thought, "Oh, I forgot to take it.
I got here and forgot.
I just remembered it again when the manager told me.
I'll go get it.
You...
I went up sometime ago.
Not today.
This way.
You'll wear this today.
It's the only way to save your life.
What do you want to do?
What are they doing?
Multivitamins.
I love it! You're so cute!
I love it.
I can't stop.
Nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah.
Please.
I'll try.
I'll do my best.
There's a Hebo-Grady in all of you.
Basic blood.
It's in all of our colors.
Indeed.
Over and out!
Yes.
I'm going to give something back.
I'd like to give it back to someone else.
I'll do my best to give it back to someone else.
Or...
"My life has been saved by the blood of people whose names and faces
"and saved my life."
Blood donors...
"Where does the blood I donated go?
"where it goes, where it's used.
How it's being used.
I don't know.
I don't think it's easy to understand how you're helping patients.
I think it's hard to understand.
The patients...
"on behalf of the patients.
I want to say thank you.
Same thing.
The same.
Same.
My man was injured and had to be hospitalized.
I had to send him a blood transfusion.
Kind.
Depends on who you ask.
It varies a lot.
He's nice, like, basically nice.
It all comes back to you in the end.
So, if you're trying to do well for other people...
It's all about you.
I knew it.
And now, on with the show.
We'll be back with another live artist.
We're going to have a lot of fun.
This is our second guest.
~~
I'll make Sun Wukong smile. I'm sure he will.
I'll give it to you... because I miss you so much.
So cute, so cute, so cute!
So cute... your smile makes me swoon...
Don't make me nervous.
Only for me.
I'm the cutest!
I'm the cutest thing since you dumped me.
This is how a girl strikes back
I'm the most adorable thing you've ever dumped me for
I'm the prettiest pokemon
I'm the cutest of all
I'm a damsel. This is a damsel striking back.
I'm the prettiest damsel in distress
Say I'm pretty now
Say I'm the prettiest damsel
Say I'm the cutest thing you've ever seen
I'm the prettiest thing you've ever seen
I'll be the prettiest and the most beautiful in my whole life
The prettiest!
A second voice plays the part of the damsel in distress.
The most lovely of all
The white ground that's more like me than anyone else
I've got wisdom to put in my hands
I can't sing with a smile, I don't want to throw up
I can't sing, I can't laugh, I can't sing, I don't want to throw up.
Whenever, whenever
It's always singing to me
I'm off to the interview.
I'm going for an interview.
I'll go.
It's the first time I've been invited, and I knew that some of the members had donated blood.
So I'm very grateful for this precious opportunity.
I have a blood donation master in my dressing room, and I'm going to donate blood at the station.
I knew about the blood donation buses and blood donation at the station, but I had never had a chance to learn about it in depth.
I had never had a chance to learn about it in depth.
I was able to learn about those things, too.
I'm sure there were many members of the publicity department there today, so I'm sure they'll be happy to learn about the importance of blood donation.
I'm sure that many members of the publicity department were there today, so I think that everyone was able to learn about the importance of blood donation.
I hope I was able to help in some small way.
I'm very happy.
I heard that Nainai-san danced for us.
We often have a lot of fun together.
Also, the number of times a song has been used and the number of views it has received...
Oh, it's 30,000! or something like that.
Everyone gets excited.
It's gone! and so on.
The numbers are going up every day.
I'm very happy to feel it day by day.
Aki-chan and I were on the bus next to each other.
I've been standing next to her for a long time.
I was standing next to her for a long time, and then I noticed...
But about a minute later, he fell down again.
Like, "I'm not leaning on you.
Yes, she was adorable.
Before the show, Oharu...
Before the show, Oharu kind of waved to me with her arms.
We walked around the stage talking.
They were walking together to the edge of the stage.
It was so cute!
Julia, I had an image of you laughing at Hiyorin's gag
I had an image of her laughing.
When Hiyorin was a little bit out of line
Julia was laughing a lot when Hiyorin was a little bit silly.
But when I make a joke
She doesn't laugh at all.
It's kind of cute to see that.
From Oharu's point of view, it's cute.
I think it's not fair.
But I think it's cute that she laughs.
It's true, the other day...
I got a new gag.
and showed it to me with a smile on her face.
smiling at me.
So cute!
The first time he did it, it wasn't very funny.
but after I kept doing it for a while
I thought, "Oh, that's good.
Slowly...
It's a little bit silly.
That's the way I feel about it.
I'd do it at home.
I'll do it at home. I'll do it at home.
That's what I like about it.
It's easy to copy. It's silly.
That's what's cute.
That's cute.
Well, what shall we eat?
By the way, I ate the pudding you sent me a while ago.
Looks delicious!
It was too much!
Aki-chan was giving it to me as she was walking.
Bon appétit!
Today, too, Mr. Ginsugi made us an example of his love and promotion!
I was the most nervous today!
That's great!
Thank you so much!
The concert was warm, but it was fun.
You're all grown up now.
I heard a rumor that Harami will be playing our song.
What's this?
I cut it all off.
There.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching
It's okay, it's okay.
You're already doing it.
You're stretching it, aren't you?
I don't know, I guess I wasn't careful enough.
I guess I didn't weigh in enough.
That's right.
You know the name.
I know Bond's path.
I thought it would be an important opportunity
I thought it would be an important opportunity and
And piano lessons.
I wanted to buy another one
In the back.
All the regulators
I was dancing to my own song.
Everyone was dancing to their own song.
Is that a camera?
Someone was filming.
A staff member was...
One of the staff was taking video.
That's what it looked like.
Thank you for joining us today.
Thank you very much for joining us today.
Thank you very much.
About blood donation
Younger generation
are donating less and less blood
blood donation is gradually decreasing
I've heard that the number of blood donors is decreasing.
I hope that we, too, can do our part
I would like to do my best to expand the circle of blood donors
I would like to do my best to expand the blood donation circle.
Thank you all very much for your time today.
Thank you, Ms. Anarin.
You can donate blood if you are 16 years old.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
After today's training...
I'm Shiryou, sir.
You are really nice!
Your fans are so warm!
You know...
What's with the inner circle of hearts?
Oh, you're buying?
That's why I'm selling it.
Maybe they make them themselves.
And people who make their own stuff.
Girl fans are so crazy.
Yes, they are.
That's amazing.
Yay!
Pilapilapilapilapilapilapilapilapilapilapilapilapilap.
Only in the middle of the most.
Oh, cancer.
Excuse me, excuse me.
I understand.
Finally, the counterattack "da.
Da. I understand.
He's dead!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
I'll see you again somewhere.
Thank you for your hard work.
Blood Donation Appreciation Live
Voices for Life
It's over.
I'm glad we were able to do it right.
It was amazing.
I learned some important new things.
We learned a lot today.
I think we learned a lot today, and I think the members of the advertising department
I think we learned a lot today.
I'm very happy to have had this opportunity.
I was very happy to have this opportunity.
I really thought about donating blood.
If you're wondering if you really want to donate blood
I'm sure there are people who are wondering if they really want to donate blood.
I'm sure there are people who are wondering if I should donate blood, too.
I'm sure there are people who are wondering if they should donate blood, even if it's just one person.
blood donation
If you donate blood...
I think there are many people who would be saved if they donated blood.
I hope you will do your best.
For one hour
I can go for about an hour.
Thank you very much.
You had a great time at the concert.
I think there were some people who saw us for the first time,
I hope to see you again.
We will do our best to be kind so that we can continue to serve the area.
Thank you very much.
I had chicken rice, milk and Nakatsuka fried chicken.
I eat a lot of rice.
It's great.
Delicious, I would like to have it.
Dumpling soup.
Chive pork.
Yeah.
ager.
Yes, yes.
Yes, thank you.
Yes.
Uma.
You look happy.
Yes.
Arrival in Tokyo at SATOUNI
See you in the next video.
We leave in 9 minutes.
I'll do my best.
Wow, such a gorgeous mobile ring.
Thank you so much!
Healy eating sweets and Hitochi trying to eat chicken tempura
Donuts
Donuts!
Here's another one!
I said the same thing.
It's Sluckey, in case you were wondering.
Let's eat.
It's so good!
I knew it would be good on the day!
Chicken tempura is so good!
It's so good!
I always eat it with salt.
Injeongnyeon!
Injonnyeon!
I cracked it up.
Oh, I didn't steal it.
It's pure lip orange.
I'll have a rice ball.
These beans are delicious!
Delicious!
This is... suntan crackers. Delicious.
This is an oil truck.
This is oil
Happy, happy, happy, happy.
Happy, happy, happy, happy
Hal's sound
Hal
Sound of Naomi Watanabe
It's so much fun!
So much fun!
I'd love to be a foot bride!
Yuu Ashimasa
Yuu Ashimasa!
It's raining, but let's have fun!
I wonder if it's raining.
It's not raining.
It's not going to rain.
What is rain?
Please, please, please...
Please come in the car.
Please, please, please
Okay.
Excuse me.
They're moving in together.
2024 We're going to perform!
It's our first time in Oita in a year.
It's been a year since I was in Oita last year.
Strange demon. The time of the entrance of the performance has changed.
It's ALO.
And...
And... of those 30/20/49 seconds.
Remember, even if it's raining, we can still smile, here we go, no matter how far we have to go
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me, the streets sparkle after the rain
I'm playing the rainbow piano...
Goodbye goodbye
by Yesterday's me, after the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a feather, my tears are making me dance, I'm wearing a rainbow dress.
La La La La...
-La La La La...